(competition in life)
(인생에서의 경쟁)
(The characters, events, groups, organizations and backgrounds of this drama are purely fictitious. We hereby inform you that)
(본 드라마에 등장하는 인물, 사건, 단체, 조직, 배경 등은 순전히 허구입니다. 이를 알려드립니다.)
very good
매우 좋은
How many people are there in total?
총 몇 명이 있나요?
There is one more
하나 더 있어요
(Episode 8)
(에피소드 8)
I'm so happy to see you, we meet here again
만나서 너무 기뻐요, 우리 여기서 다시 만나요
Yes, Director Goo
네, 구 감독님
sit down
앉아
Nice to meet the people from the task force
태스크 포스 사람들을 만나서 반가워요
Then let's get started
그럼 시작해 볼까요
No matter what kind of organization it is, it will have its own unique characteristics.
어떤 조직이던 간에 그 조직은 고유한 특성을 갖고 있습니다.
What makes an organization work is its members
조직을 작동시키는 것은 구성원이다
Yes, that is, people
그래요, 사람들이요
In addition, it is also the members who can create the characteristics of the organization.
또한, 조직의 특성을 만들어내는 것도 구성원이다.
In the organization…
조직에서는…
I have someone I like
좋아하는 사람이 있어요
The guy I met in San Diego
샌디에이고에서 만난 남자
I saw her again
나는 그녀를 다시 보았다
I'm attracted to her again
나는 또 그 사람에게 끌린다.
Started to care about her again
그녀에게 다시 관심이 생기기 시작했어요
Think about what kind of company you want to work for
어떤 회사에 입사하고 싶은지 생각해 보세요
That is the organizational culture we will build in the future
그것이 미래에 우리가 만들어갈 조직문화입니다.
But this...
하지만 이것은...
What if it is for the sustainable development of the business and the creation of profits?
기업의 지속가능한 발전 과 수익창출을 위한 것이라면 어떨까요 ?
I want to be like her in the future
나는 미래에 그녀처럼되고 싶다
She should have also produced company publications in the beginning.
그녀는 처음에 회사 출판물도 제작했어야 했습니다.
Hello
안녕하세요
You were suffering a lot during this period, right?
그동안 많이 고생하셨죠?
No, it's okay with me
아니, 난 괜찮아
What should you do if you really want to be appreciated by your boss?
상사로부터 정말로 인정받고 싶다면 어떻게 해야 합니까 ?
etc…
등…
Park Yoon-soo was present...
박윤수가 참석했다..
The problem is that our levels are different
문제는 레벨이 다르다는 거
Her rank is much higher than mine
그 사람 순위가 나보다 훨씬 높아
But isn’t that what everyone does?
그런데 그건 누구나 하는 일 아닙니까?
Want to show your best side and be recognized by others
자신의 가장 좋은 모습을 보여주고 싶고 , 남들에게 인정받고 싶다
In other words, if you are willing, the company will change.
즉, 당신이 의지만 있다면 회사는 바뀔 것이다.
And you should build the company in the direction you want.
그리고 당신 이 원하는 방향으로 회사를 세워야 한다.
I hope everyone will first think about what their dream company looks like.
다들 자신이 꿈꾸는 회사가 어떤 모습일지 먼저 생각해보시길 바랍니다 .
That will be part of the internal culture improvement program
이는 내부 문화 개선 프로그램의 일부가 될 것입니다.
beginning
시작
First, the team leader responsible for the project must be selected
먼저 해당 프로젝트를 담당할 팀장을 선정해야 합니다.
Does anyone volunteer?
자원봉사하는 사람이 있나요?
I'm willing to give it a try
나는 그것을 시도해 볼 의향이 있습니다
If everyone agrees
모두가 동의한다면
-What do you think? -I agree
-어떻게 생각하나요? -나는 동의한다
Of course I agree
물론 나도 동의한다
Okay, I'll let you do it.
좋아요, 그렇게 하도록 하겠습니다.
Miss Park Yun Zhao?
박윤자씨?
Um?
음?
Yes, I agree too
응, 나도 동의해
Okay, then it’s decided
알았어 그럼 결정됐어
- I'll leave everything to you - Okay
- 모든 걸 당신에게 맡길게요 - 알았어
Let’s briefly discuss it here today.
오늘은 여기서 간략히 살펴보겠습니다.
OK
좋아요
Thanks for your hard work
당신의 노고에 감사드립니다
Okay, I'll go first then
알았어, 그럼 나 먼저 갈게
Then please let the team leader know the date of the next meeting of the task force.
그런 다음 팀 리더에게 다음 태스크 포스 회의 날짜를 알려주십시오 .
I will create another group chat room
그룹채팅방을 하나 더 만들겠습니다
Okay, everyone has worked hard.
그렇군요 다들 고생하셨습니다.
-Thank you for your hard work - Yes, thank you for your hard work
- 수고해 주셔서 감사합니다 - 네, 수고해 주셔서 감사합니다
(Flexible salary reward system)
(유연한 급여 보상 시스템)
(This system allows employees to decide their workload at the beginning of the month and the performance evaluation results will be reflected in their salary)
(월초에 직원들이 업무량을 결정하고 , 성과평가 결과를 급여에 반영하는 제도입니다.)
(The team leader has the right to conduct individual comprehensive performance evaluation)
(팀장은 개인별 종합 성과평가를 실시할 권리가 있습니다.)
As you can see, each group is responsible for a different project
보시다시피 각 그룹은 서로 다른 프로젝트를 담당합니다.
The team leader and team members can decide the workload of their own projects
팀장과 팀원이 각자의 프로젝트 업무량을 결정할 수 있습니다.
In addition, individual comprehensive performance evaluation is also closely related to salary.
또한, 개인별 종합 성과평가 도 급여와 밀접한 관련이 있습니다.
So will your monthly work performance be directly reflected in that month’s salary?
그러면 월별 업무 성과가 그 달 월급에 바로 반영되나요?
right
오른쪽
That means you get as much as you do, right?
즉, 받은 만큼만 받는다는 뜻이죠?
Yes, there will be group evaluations every month
네, 매달 그룹 평가가 있을 예정입니다
The larger the project size the team is responsible for
팀이 담당하는 프로젝트 규모가 클수록
The income will be more
수입은 더 많아지겠죠
Salaries should also be increased accordingly
급여도 그에 맞게 인상되어야 한다
In addition, this also contributes to the importance of personal time
또한 이는 개인 시간의 중요성에도 기여합니다.
People who aspire to achieve a balance between work and life are better
일과 삶의 균형을 추구하는 사람이 더 좋습니다.
how do you feel?
기분이 어때요?
Are you willing to reconsider quitting your job now?
지금 직장을 그만두는 것을 다시 고려해 볼 의향이 있습니까?
Are you busy now?
지금 바쁘신가요?
Why?
왜?
Isn't there usually no one in the store at this time?
보통 이 시간에는 가게에 사람이 없지 않나요?
Why are you so busy?
왜 그렇게 바쁜가요?
Otherwise, come over and help me.
그렇지 않으면 와서 나를 도와주세요.
But I want to talk to you
하지만 난 당신과 얘기하고 싶어요
hateful
증오스러운
When am I during your working hours?
근무시간 중 나는 언제 있나요?
Are you asking me to listen to my complaints?
내 불만을 들어달라고 요청하는 겁니까?
No, I mean...
아니 그게 아니라 내 말은...
If you're just going to whine then I'm hanging up, I'm busy
징징거릴 거면 끊을게 바빠
Really, a heartless woman
참으로 마음이 없는 여자
(Call records)
(통화 기록)
Am I so friendless to begin with?
나는 처음부터 그렇게 친구가 없는 걸까?
Oh my god, Park Yoon So.
맙소사, 박윤소.
Look how badly your people live.
당신네 사람들이 얼마나 나쁘게 살고 있는지 보세요.
(Website manager: Lee Ha Eun Jae Min, SEA Marketing Team: Kim Min Soo)
(홈페이지 관리자 : 이하은 재민, SEA 마케팅팀 : 김민수)
(Representative Kim Hee-young)
(대표 김희영)
Representative Kim, it’s me
김 대표님, 나예요
The stickiest chewing gum for you
당신을 위한 가장 끈적한 츄잉껌
Where are you?
어디세요?
Oh my god
맙소사
How do I look?
나 어때 보여?
-Thanks, Yun Zhao . -It's very good.
- 고마워요, 윤자오 - 아주 좋아요.
Yun Zhao, do you know how to do Taekwondo?
자오윤 씨, 태권도 할 줄 아세요?
Yes, because of my grandmother
응, 할머니 때문에
I have been told since I was a child that girls should be powerful
나는 어렸을 때부터 여자는 강해야 한다는 말을 들어왔습니다.
So she first sent me to learn Taekwondo
그래서 처음에 태권도 배우라고 저한테 보냈어요.
Your grandma?
당신의 할머니?
Yun Zhao, it seems that you lived with your grandmother when you were a child.
윤자오 씨는 어렸을 때 할머니와 함께 살았던 것 같아요 .
Because the man my mother was dating at the time didn't like children.
왜냐하면 당시 어머니가 사귀던 남자는 아이들을 좋아하지 않았기 때문입니다.
She entrusted me to my grandmother
그녀는 나를 할머니에게 맡겼다
Tied
묶여
You can go get spanked now
지금 가서 때려도 돼
Stand at attention and salute the other person
차렷 자세로 서서 상대방에게 경의를 표하세요
Prepare
준비하다
start
시작
Wait, wait a minute!
잠깐, 잠깐만!
No, wait a minute...
아니, 잠깐만요...
-Cheers
-건배
So what rank are you in?
그럼 당신은 어떤 계급에 속해 있나요?
Of course it's a black belt
물론 검은띠죠
Oh my god
맙소사
It turns out there is a martial artist here. Our Yun Zhao is really handsome.
여기 무술가가 있다는 걸 알고 보니 우리 윤자오가 정말 잘생겼어요.
But I've forgotten all about it now
하지만 지금은 다 잊어버렸어
But when I was in elementary school, I was really good at kicking.
그런데 초등학교 때는 발차기를 정말 잘했어요.
Like the little girl just now?
지금 어린 소녀처럼요?
So you have been living with grandma since then ?
그럼 그 이후로 할머니와 함께 살고 계시나요 ?
I moved to Seoul when I was in fifth grade.
저는 5학년 때 서울로 이사했어요.
My mom was dating another man at the time
엄마는 그때 다른 남자랑 사귀고 있었어
And that man
그리고 그 사람
willing to accept me
기꺼이 나를 받아들인다
I miss my grandma so much. I haven’t seen her for a long time.
저는 할머니가 너무 보고 싶어요. 오랫동안 뵙지 못했어요.
Yes, go visit her quickly
응, 빨리 그 사람한테 가봐
She may not be able to wait for you there forever
그녀는 그곳에서 영원히 당신을 기다리지 못할 수도 있습니다
But didn’t you come to me just because you had something to say?
그런데 그냥 할 말이 있어서 나한테 온 거 아니었어?
-Here are the two soju cocktails you ordered . -Thank you.
- 주문하신 소주 칵테일 두 잔입니다 . - 감사합니다.
-What did you order? -We also have two soju cocktails
-무엇을 주문하셨나요? - 소주 칵테일도 두 잔 있어요
-That's right... -That's right
-맞아요... -맞아요
I am coming!
나는 간다!
Why did you come now?
왜 지금 왔나요?
-Hello! -Give me another cocktail, please
-안녕하세요! - 칵테일 한 잔 더 주세요
Okay, send it over right away
알았어, 지금 바로 보내줘
-Hey, Xiao En! -Um
-안녕, 샤오엔! -음
Hey, what's going on?
이봐 무슨 일이야?
how so? This is how the same thing?
어떻게 그래? 이것은 어떻게 같은 것입니까?
I don't know, it seems to be an actor or a singer
모르겠어요 배우나 가수인 것 같아요
Introduce my bar on social media
나의 바를 SNS에 소개해보세요
Said this is a good place to bring your own food and drinks
이곳은 음식과 음료를 직접 가져오기 좋은 곳이라고 하더군요
Hey, don't just stand there stupidly, come be a waiter.
야, 멍청하게 거기 서있지 말고, 와서 웨이터가 되어라.
-me? -Hello
-나? -안녕하세요
I don't have time to help customers order food right now
지금은 고객이 음식을 주문하는 것을 도와줄 시간이 없습니다
- Come on - Hey, which table is this?
- 어서 - 야, 이게 무슨 테이블이야?
- That table over there - Got it!
- 저기 테이블 - 알았어요!
-good! -Xiao En
-좋은! -샤오엔
-You're here. -What's going on here? how so?
- 여기 있었군요 - 무슨 일이에요? 어떻게 그래?
Business is booming here, but you keep questioning it
여기서 사업은 호황을 누리고 있지만 계속 의문을 품고 있습니다.
It makes people feel uncomfortable.
사람들의 기분을 불편하게 만듭니다.
A celebrity uploaded a post about Utopia on his social media
한 연예인이 자신의 SNS에 유토피아에 대한 글을 올렸다.
OK, understood
알았어, 이해했어
Do you need help?
도움이 필요하신가요?
Of course, it's very necessary, please
물론 매우 필요한 일입니다.
Please order for me, please
저 대신 주문해주세요
order
주문하다
Is there anyone who hasn’t ordered yet?
아직 주문 안하신 분 계시나요?
-Raise your hand, please -me!
-손을 들어주세요 .
Please raise your hand!
손을 들어주세요!
come on
어서 해봐요
Which table is this from?
이건 어느 테이블에서 나온 거예요?
good
좋은
- here's your beer - thank you
- 맥주 여기 있어요 - 고마워요
Hey, the drinks haven't been served to those two yet.
아, 아직 그 두 사람에게는 음료가 제공되지 않았습니다.
I’m bringing you a cocktail, would you like to put it here?
칵테일 가져올 건데 여기에 넣어 드릴까요?
Please enjoy
즐기세요
-Can I take a photo with you? -me? Why do you want to take pictures with me?
- 같이 사진 좀 찍어도 될까요? -나? 왜 나랑 사진 찍고 싶어?
Because you are handsome
왜냐면 당신은 잘생겼거든요
Hey, snap shot
야, 스냅샷
I moved to Seoul when I was in fifth grade and met him at school for the first time.
나는 5학년 때 서울로 이사했고 학교에서 처음 그를 만났다.
At that time, I thought to myself, "How can any boy be so good-looking?"
그때 '어쩜 남자가 이렇게 잘생길 수 있지?'라는 생각이 들었습니다.
His skin is really white
피부 진짜 하얗다
And I was running around in the countryside all day long
그리고 하루종일 시골을 뛰어다녔어요
-You are so tanned. -You are so handsome.
- 너 너무 검게 그을렸어 - 너 정말 잘생겼어
you are really handsome
당신은 정말 잘생겼어요
but…
하지만…
one two three
하나 둘 셋
The most charming thing is
가장 매력적인 점은
his beautiful eyes
그의 아름다운 눈
(2001, 12-year-old Yunzhao and Xiaoen)
(2001년, 12세 윤자오와 샤오엔)
Is today's lunch delicious?
오늘 점심 맛있나요?
yes
예
Which side dish do you think is the most delicious?
여러분은 어떤 반찬이 가장 맛있다고 생각하시나요?
sausage
소시지
-Hey, look at me! -Oh, I think that's delicious too.
-야, 나 좀 봐! -아, 그것도 맛있을 것 같아.
Damn it, how many times do you want me to say it?
젠장, 내가 몇 번이나 말하길 바라나요?
-Hey, I asked you to look at me -Hey, raise your head
-야, 나 좀 봐달라고 했어. -야, 고개 좀 들어봐
-Hello!
-안녕하세요!
- Come on - Where do you want to go?
- 어서 - 어디로 가고 싶니?
What not to do? Where do you want to run?
하지 말아야 할 것은 무엇입니까? 어디로 달리고 싶나요?
-You don't want to go anywhere. -I heard your dad went to jail.
- 아무데도 가고 싶지 않잖아 - 아버지가 감옥에 갔다고 들었어
Isn't he from our class?
그 사람 우리 반 출신 아닌가요?
Yes, Yoo Jae-min
응 유재민
That very fair-skinned Yoo Jae-min who always comes first in exams?
항상 시험에서 1등을 하는 그 하얀 피부의 유재민?
You can't judge a person by his skin color
피부색으로 사람을 판단하면 안 돼요
-Hey, are you going to visit the prison? -Are you going to jail too?
-야, 감옥에 갈 거야? -너도 감옥에 갈 거야?
Why are they bothering him?
왜 그들은 그를 괴롭히는 걸까요?
Hey, where do you want to run?
야, 어디로 달리고 싶니?
- We're having fun. - Lift your head up.
- 우리는 즐거운 시간을 보내고 있어요 - 고개를 들어보세요.
- Lift your head up - Jae Min's father is in jail
- 고개를 들어보세요 - 재민 아버지가 감옥에 갇혔어요
Where are you going?
어디 가세요?
Damn it!
젠장!
-They're all kids from around here. -Where do you want to go?
- 다 이 근처 애들이에요 - 어디로 가고 싶어요?
- Stay calm - don't move!
- 침착하세요 - 움직이지 마세요!
They probably thought it was embarrassing to live in the same neighborhood as him.
아마 그와 같은 동네에 사는 것이 부끄럽다고 생각했을 것이다.
It was his father who was going to jail, why should he be tortured?
감옥에 갈 사람은 그의 아버지인데 왜 고문을 받아야합니까?
Hello! Let him go!
안녕하세요! 그분을 석방시켜 주시 ​​오!
Why don't you let go quickly?
빨리 놔주는 게 어때?
-I said let him go! -etc…
-그를 놔주라고 했어! -등…
Hello
안녕하세요
Wait, hey!
잠깐, 이봐요!
They are all students from the nearby dojo.
그들은 모두 근처 도장에서 온 학생들입니다.
You stink...
너 냄새나...
Hello!
안녕하세요!
do not Cry
울지 마세요
It's not your fault that your dad is in jail.
네 아버지가 감옥에 있는 것은 네 잘못이 아니야.
There were tears in his eyes
그의 눈에는 눈물이 고였습니다
The eyes that look at me are shining
나를 바라보는 눈빛이 빛나고 있어
I felt a numbness in my chest
가슴이 저릿해지는 느낌이 들었어
It’s the innocence of a 12-year-old
12살의 순수함이다
I fell in love with him just like that
나는 그 사람과 사랑에 빠졌어요
But you confessed to him but he was rejected?
그런데 그 사람한테 고백했는데 거절당했다고요?
You should have confessed earlier
좀 더 일찍 고백했어야 했는데
Take advantage of the wonderful years in your teens or 20s
10대나 20대의 멋진 시절을 즐겨보세요
There's a long and complicated reason
길고 복잡한 이유가 있어요
But in one word
그런데 한마디로
It's just not the right time
단지 때가 아닐 뿐이야
"opportunity"
"기회"
Of course timing is important
물론 타이밍이 중요하지만
anyway
그래도
This is actually not what I want to tell you today.
사실 제가 오늘 말씀드리고 싶은 것은 이게 아닙니다.
Well, what else?
글쎄, 또 뭐야?
Just say it, tell it all so that you won't get sick from boredom
그냥 말해, 다 말해줘 심심해서 아프지 않게
Jae Min rejected me because he had someone , right?
재민이는 좋아하는 사람이 ?
right
오른쪽
But the person he likes is actually the chief public relations officer of our company
그런데 그 사람이 좋아하는 사람이 사실 우리 회사 홍보실장 이에요.
Chief public relations officer, she has a very high position
홍보담당관, 그녀는 매우 높은 지위에 있다
Not only that, I entered this industry as a role model.
뿐만 아니라 저는 이 업계에 롤모델로 들어왔습니다.
Do you know Goo Yi Jung?
구이정을 아시나요?
- Representative Kim, are you okay? - Um, sorry.
- 김 의원님, 괜찮으세요? - 음, 미안해요.
Oh my god
맙소사
This world is so small
이 세상은 너무 작아요
That one, Goo Yi Jung
그 사람, 구이정
He was a colleague who joined the newspaper office at the same time as me.
그는 나와 같은 시기에 신문사에 입사한 동료였다.
What?
무엇?
Um
음
Thank you for your hard work
당신의 노고에 감사드립니다
I'm going to have a cigarette and then come back
담배 한 대 피우고 돌아올게요
Do you like it here so much?
여기가 그렇게 마음에 드나요?
really weird
정말 이상해
When you drink, don’t you always pay attention to the food that goes with your drinks?
술을 마실 때, 술과 어울리는 음식에 항상 주의를 기울이지 않나요?
There's not even any food or drinks here.
여기에는 음식이나 음료도 없습니다.
But there is something incomparable
하지만 비교할 수 없는 것이 있다
Hello
안녕하세요
You are her friend, so you should know
당신은 그녀의 친구이므로 알아야합니다
If I told Xiao En that I liked her, what do you think she would say?
내가 샤오은에게 좋아한다고 말하면 그녀는 뭐라고 말할 것 같나요?
"Shut up and go away", is this the case?
"닥치고 가세요" 이런 경우인가요?
But the person you dated before...
그런데 예전에 사귀던 그 사람이..
Yes, it's a man
응, 남자야
That's not important
그건 중요하지 않아요
So what exactly are you trying to say?
그렇다면 정확히 무엇을 말하려는 걸까요?
Do you want me to help you test her?
내가 그녀를 테스트하는 것을 도와줄까요?
No, why are you asking for me? Of course I have to ask myself
아니, 왜 나한테 물어보는 거야? 물론 나 자신에게 물어봐야지
if not?
그렇지 않다면?
I want you to tell me what type of person Xiao En likes.
샤오은이 어떤 사람을 좋아하는지 말해주세요 .
The type like you...
당신같은 타입은...
She should like it
그녀는 그것을 좋아해야 해
-Yeah? -right
-응? -오른쪽
Is she not heterosexual?
그 사람 이성애자 아닌가?
Hey, that's the question you should ask yourself
아, 그건 네가 스스로에게 물어봐야 할 질문이야
It's not my place to answer
그건 내가 대답할 자리가 아니야
Just pretend you don’t know first.
일단은 모르는 척 하세요.
Xiao En, aren't you hungry? Would you like to order some takeout?
샤오엔 씨, 배고프지 않나요? 테이크아웃을 주문하시겠습니까?
I want to eat very spicy chicken feet now
나 지금 엄청 매운 닭발 먹고 싶어
Chicken feet? no problem
닭 발? 괜찮아요
Hey, where's Yun Zhao?
야, 자오윤은 어디 있어?
I was about to ask you
너한테 물어보려고 했는데
Why isn't Yun Zhao here?
윤자오는 왜 여기 없나요?
I'm here to find her
나는 그녀를 찾으러 여기 있어요
She seems to be in a bad mood today
오늘 그 사람 기분이 안 좋은 것 같아
Why?
왜?
Her rejection by you should come to an end.
당신의 그녀의 거절은 끝나야합니다.
I guess something happened to her today
오늘 그 사람한테 무슨 일이 있었던 것 같아
got rejected? Who?
거절당했어? WHO?
I go first
내가 먼저 가
Who was rejected?
거절당한 사람은 누구입니까?
Have you rejected someone else again?
또 다른 사람을 거절했나요?
It seems this guy is still very popular
이 사람 아직도 인기가 많은 것 같아요
No, I was rejected too
아니, 나도 거절당했어
God, this is interesting.
맙소사, 이거 흥미롭네요.
That's enough. You two should enjoy the spicy chicken feet.
이쯤되면 둘이서 매콤한 닭발을 즐겨보세요.
I'm leaving
나는 떠난다
Who? Who rejected him?
WHO? 누가 그를 거부했는가?
I don't know either
나도 모르겠어요
-Really -when will the delivery arrive?
- 정말 - 배송은 언제 도착하나요?
About 30 minutes?
약 30분?
when we met again by chance in new york
뉴욕에서 우연히 다시 만났을 때
We also drank wine together
와인도 같이 마셨는데
I thought I had completely forgotten you
난 너를 완전히 잊어버린 줄 알았는데
wrong
잘못된
It's me trying my best to forget you
너를 잊으려고 최선을 다하는 건 나야
Because just thinking about you makes me uncomfortable
너만 생각하면 불편하니까
But recently
하지만 최근에는
It keeps popping up in my mind
자꾸만 머릿속에 떠오른다
those beautiful moments
그 아름다운 순간들
Cai Min
카이 민
I know to say that
나는 그렇게 말할 줄 안다
sorry for you
미안해
but I
하지만 나는
impossible
불가능한
I won’t be your lover again
난 다시는 네 연인이 되지 않을 거야
If that's what you're looking forward to
그것이 당신이 기대하는 것이라면
I think I need to make it clear to you clearly
내 생각엔 내가 너에게 확실히 알려줘야 할 것 같아
You also had this look at that time
그때도 똑같은 표정이었어
When you break up with me
나랑 헤어질 때
I get it now
이제 이해가된다
As long as your eyes remain firm, no matter how hard I pester you
너의 눈빛이 굳건하기만 하면 내가 아무리 괴롭혀도
You won't change your mind
당신은 마음을 바꾸지 않을 것입니다
I was too young then
그때는 너무 어렸어
The future is filled with confusion and uneasiness
혼란과 불안으로 가득한 미래
But now many things are different
하지만 지금은 많은 것들이 달라졌어
therefore
그러므로
That’s why I have expectations
그래서 기대가 되네요
If you ever need someone to have a meal or a drink with, you can give me a call.
혹시 함께 식사나 술 한잔 할 사람이 필요하시면 저에게 전화하세요.
I want to be your friend
나는 당신의 친구가되고 싶어
I'm glad your reaction was more calm than I thought.
생각보다 반응이 차분해서 다행이네요.
If only I hadn't been so pretentious
내가 그렇게 가식적이지 않았더라면
It would look pathetic
한심해 보일 텐데
good
좋은
See you at our company
우리 회사에서 만나요
To be honest, the so-called human heart
솔직히 말해서 소위 인간의 마음은
really complicated
정말 복잡하다
When I heard about her from Caimin
카이민에게서 그녀에 대한 소식을 들었을 때
I feel resentful and jealous
원망과 질투를 느낀다
So what do you want to do?
그럼 당신은 무엇을 하고 싶나요?
I understand that you feel very complicated now and you can't help but care about them.
나는 당신이 지금 매우 복잡하다고 느끼고 그들에 대해 신경 쓰지 않을 수 없다는 것을 이해합니다.
but…
하지만…
Those are your emotions
그게 당신의 감정이에요
In fact, it has nothing to do with the two of them , right?
사실 두 사람과는 아무 관련이 없잖아요 ?
Yes, that's right
네, 맞습니다
you're right
네가 옳아
I still want to be appreciated by Director Goo and be recognized by her
그래도 구감독님께 인정받고 싶고 , 인정받고 싶어요.
It seems that I just need to sort out my feelings for Xiaomin as soon as possible.
하루라도 빨리 샤오민에 대한 감정을 정리하면 될 것 같습니다 .
But don’t push yourself too hard, you know?
하지만 너무 무리하지는 마세요. 아시죠?
Sometimes letting yourself go and following your feelings is a good way
때로는 자신을 내버려두고 감정을 따르는 것이 좋은 방법입니다.
I want to let go of this relationship quickly now
이제 빨리 이 관계를 놓아버리고 싶어
Hello everyone
안녕하세요
You can sit outside
밖에 앉아도 돼
-Okay, I got it, over there -Thank you
-알았어, 저기 있어 - 고마워
Okay, thank you
좋아 감사합니다
Representative Xu
쉬 대표
-Do you want to sit outside? -OK
-밖에 앉으시겠어요? -좋아요
Masaaki
允昭
It’s you, Donghun!
바로 너야, 동훈아!
Is everyone here together?
여기 모두가 함께 있나요?
-Senior -Oh, wait...
-선배 -아, 잠깐...
Let's sit over there
저기에 앉자
-Is everyone here? Got it - talk to you later
-다들 왔나요? 알았어 . 나중에 얘기하자
I'm going to say hello and I'll be back soon. Wait for me.
인사하고 곧 돌아올테니 기다려주세요.
-Hello - are you all here? Did you just finish working overtime?
- 안녕하세요 -다들 오셨나요? 방금 초과 근무를 마쳤나요?
-Yep _
-응 _
Oh, thank you for your hard work.
아, 노고에 감사드립니다.
-You should treat them to something delicious. -That's what I mean.
- 맛있는 음식을 대접해야 해요 - 그게 내 말이에요.
Well, actually today I
음, 사실 오늘 나는
Went to learn Taekwondo
태권도 배우러 갔어요
-Taekwondo?
-태권도요?
I'm still sparring with someone today
나 오늘도 누군가와 스파링 중이야
The opponent is a petite elementary school girl
상대는 몸집이 작은 초등학생
But I keep running away
하지만 난 계속 도망쳐
- And I got a lot of beatings - Oh my god
- 그리고 구타도 많이 당했어요 - 맙소사
-It's so miserable -because I was too busy running away...
-너무 비참해요 -도망치기 바빠서...
Senior was stuck with them, so I came here in her place, is that okay?
선배가 꼼짝도 안 해서 내가 대신 왔는데, 괜찮아?
I will never learn Taekwondo again
나는 다시는 태권도를 배우지 않을 것이다
I don't want to learn anymore
더 이상 배우고 싶지 않아요
-thanks , thanks
-감사 감사
You don't have to care about me
나한테 신경쓰지 않아도 돼
I've drunk enough, it's time to go
충분히 취했으니 이제 갈 시간이야
This is not okay
이건 안 돼
It took a lot of effort for us to meet each other. You can't leave so quickly.
우리가 만나기까지 많은 노력이 필요했습니다. 그렇게 빨리 떠날 수는 없습니다.
Let’s have a toast first
먼저 건배하자
This is unfair
불공평 해
I've been drinking it since just now.
방금부터 마시고 있어요.
Okay, then I have to catch up with you
알았어, 그럼 따라잡아야겠어
No, that's not what I meant...
아니, 그런 뜻은 아니었는데...
You don't have to do that
그렇게 할 필요는 없어
-Wait a minute- Representative Kim, thank you so much today.
-잠깐만- 김 대표님, 오늘 정말 감사드립니다.
I should be the one sending you back
너를 돌려보내는 사람은 나여야만 해
-I didn't expect that today would be... -Ouch
- 오늘이 이렇게 될 줄은 몰랐는데... - 아야
Hello
안녕하세요
Are you going to abandon me?
나를 버리실 건가요?
-Where is a good place to go? -No la…
-가기 좋은 곳은 어디인가요? -아니 라…
-Absolutely not like that- Representative Kim, we...
-절대 그렇지 않습니다- 김 대표님, 우리는...
That's what you do
그게 당신이 하는 일이에요
-Right? -That's it for today
-오른쪽? -오늘은 여기까지야
-You have to go home directly . Seeing that you are in such a hurry to see me off, I guessed it right.
- 집에 바로 가셔야 해요 . 날 배웅하려고 그렇게 서두르시는 걸 보니 맞을 것 같았어요.
I'll contact you again
다시 연락할게요
-Please send her back safely. - Representative Kim, walk carefully and slowly.
- 무사히 돌려보내주세요 - 김 대표님, 조심해서 천천히 걸어주세요.
-Be careful when you go home. -I can treat you
- 집에 갈 때 조심하세요 .
- Be careful when you go home - Goodbye
- 안녕
-Okay, thank you for your hard work . -Yes, thank you.
-알겠습니다. 수고해 주셔서 감사합니다 . -네, 감사합니다.
-Then let's go . -Goodbye
-그럼 가자 .
Okay, go and renew the stall
알았어 가서 스톨을 갱신해
-Renew the share? -Do you want to renew your stall?
-공유를 갱신하시겠습니까? - 실속을 갱신하고 싶나요?
- ok - let's go
- 확인 가자
Won't you go with them?
그들과 함께 가지 않을래?
At times like this, I should know better and avoid them.
이럴 땐 더 잘 알고 피해야겠습니다.
I get it, "the boss is lonely"
알겠습니다 "사장님은 외로워요"
Would you like to find another place to have a drink?
술 한잔할 다른 곳을 찾아보시겠어요?
Alas
아아
I think it's time for you to go back
이제 돌아갈 때가 된 것 같아
No, I'm really fine
아니, 난 정말 괜찮아
I drank a lot just to keep up with your progress.
나는 단지 당신의 발전을 따라잡기 위해 술을 많이 마셨습니다.
So, you drank too fast
그럼 너 너무 빨리 마셨구나
Oh my God, where is your home?
맙소사, 집이 어디예요?
No, it's okay, I have to take you home
아냐 괜찮아 집에 데려다줘야 해
Representative Xu, tell me your address quickly.
쉬 대표님, 주소를 빨리 알려주세요.
I'm fine
잘 지내요
No, you're in trouble
아니, 문제가 생겼어
Oh my god
맙소사
Uncle driver, please take him to Jamsil
운전기사 삼촌, 잠실까지 데려다 주세요
You can't leave him alone
그 사람을 내버려 둘 수는 없어요
OK, I'll go with him
알았어, 내가 그 사람이랑 같이 갈게
Have you arrived at the company?
회사에 도착하셨나요?
Come meet me in the stairwell
계단통에서 나를 만나러 오세요
Hey, here I come
안녕, 나 왔어
What's up?
무슨 일이야?
What's wrong? What's the matter?
뭐가 문제 야? 무슨 일이야?
I'm going to be exhausted
나는 지칠 것이다
Why don't you take the elevator instead of running up?
달려가는 대신 엘리베이터를 타는 게 어때요?
What?
무엇?
That is to say
즉 말하자면
Isn't there a task force meeting later?
나중에 태스크포스 회의가 있지 않나요?
We will continue to meet at the company in the future
앞으로도 계속 회사에서 만나자
So I think we need to make it clear
그래서 우리는 분명히 해야 한다고 생각해요
I plan to keep my distance from you for a while.
당분간은 너랑 거리를 둘 생각이야.
Even if we are friends, it is necessary
친구라도 이건 꼭 필요한 거야
It's just to make me feel more comfortable, I know it's selfish
그냥 내 기분을 편하게 하려는 것 뿐이야, 이기적인 거 알아
Sorry for you too...
너도 미안해...
No way
안 돼요
do what you want to do
네가 원하는 것을해라
You can do whatever you want
당신은 당신이 원하는 무엇이든 할 수 있습니다
I know how to pretend like nothing happened
아무 일도 없었던 척 하는 법도 알아
In fact, it’s even more difficult
사실 그게 더 어렵다.
Just do what you want
그냥 원하는 대로 하세요
Hey, are you going to fight again?
야, 또 싸울 거야?
How old are you, why are you still fighting with others?
당신은 몇 살인데 왜 아직도 다른 사람들과 싸우고 있습니까?
That is to say
즉 말하자면
So…
그래서…
I go first
내가 먼저 가
Masaaki
允昭
But I still want to say
하지만 나는 아직도 말하고 싶다
Don't make me wait too long
너무 오래 기다리게 만들지 마세요
I thought about it carefully
곰곰히 생각해보니
Found out that I actually don’t have any friends
알고보니 친구가 하나도 없었다
-Hello, Representative Kim -Hello
-안녕하세요, 김 대표님 -안녕하세요.
Good morning
좋은 아침이에요
Did you get home safely yesterday?
어제 집에 무사히 도착하셨나요?
- Yes, Representative Kim - Huh?
- 네, 김 대표님 - 응?
Representative Xu, what happened yesterday?
쉬 대표님, 어제 무슨 일이 있었나요?
Didn’t I leave first yesterday?
어제 나 먼저 안 갔지?
Yeah
응
As soon as he walked into the company just now, I was shocked.
지금 막 회사에 들어오자마자 깜짝 놀랐어요.
-Why? -You'll know when you go in and take a look.
-왜? -들어가서 보시면 아실 거예요.
Please come in
오세요
Representative Xu, what happened to you yesterday?
쉬 대표님, 어제 무슨 일이 있었나요?
Representative Xu
쉬 대표
Oh my God, what happened to your face?
맙소사, 얼굴에 무슨 일이 일어난 거죠?
I rolled around in the rose bushes
나는 장미 덤불 사이를 뒹굴었다.
What?
무엇?
There are roses planted in the flower beds of our apartment
우리 아파트 화단에는 장미가 심어져 있어요
I rolled around there
나는 거기에서 굴러다녔다
how so?
어떻게 그래?
Representative Xu
쉬 대표
No, I'm fine
아냐 난 괜찮아
My home has arrived
내 집이 도착했어요
-Then go in . -Goodbye
-그럼 들어가세요 .
really weird
정말 이상해
Not over there
거기 말고
This has to be opened
이건 열어야 해
Representative Xu
쉬 대표
The door isn't over there
문은 저기가 아니야
On your right
너의 오른쪽에
OK, bye
알았어 잘가
good
좋은
-Why can't this be opened? -It's the right side
-이건 왜 열리지 않나요? -오른쪽이에요
Right, yes right
그렇죠, 그렇죠
Representative Xu!
쉬 대표님!
-Representative Xu -Yes
-쉬 대표 -네
Are you OK?
괜찮으세요?
if it were me
나라면
Can't remember anything
아무것도 기억나지 않는다
that's better
그게 낫다
Alas
아아
Hello
안녕하세요
I think Yun Zhao must have suffered a lot.
윤자오님도 많이 고생하셨을 것 같아요.
Alas
아아
Have you been to the hospital?
병원에 가보셨나요?
If you haven't gone yet, you should go there as soon as possible before the wound worsens.
아직 가지 못했다면 상처가 더 심해지기 전에 최대한 빨리 그곳으로 가야 한다.
Also, don’t forget to treat Yun Zhao to a delicious meal, you know?
그리고 윤자오에게 맛있는 식사 대접하는 것도 잊지 마세요.
Do I have to treat me to make amends?
보상하려면 나를 치료해야 합니까?
Alas, of course
아아, 물론이지
Please order something delicious
맛있는거 주문해주세요
It looks like you need to stop drinking for a while, you know?
당분간 술을 끊어야 할 것 같군요.
( Weekly schedule of the Internal Culture Improvement Project Task Force)
( 내부문화개선사업TF 주간 일정)
Okay, then before the next meeting, everyone is asked to formulate the questions for the questionnaire.
좋아요, 그러면 다음 회의 전에 모든 사람에게 설문지에 대한 질문을 작성하도록 요청합니다.
Can I make a comment?
댓글을 달 수 있나요?
Compared with the positive effects of internal culture improvement projects
내부문화개선사업 의 긍정적 효과 와 비교
The company’s employees don’t seem to pay much attention
회사 직원들이 별로 관심을 두지 않는 것 같아요
In addition to our public relations team and human resources team
당사 홍보팀, 인사팀 외에
No one else seems to know this project is going on
이 프로젝트가 진행되고 있다는 것을 아무도 모르는 것 같아요
Is it because we just started trying it?
우리가 이제 막 시도하기 시작했기 때문인가요?
So after thinking about it
그래서 생각한 끝에
came up with one
하나를 생각해 냈어
Activities that can heat up the topic before the survey
설문조사 전 화제를 뜨겁게 달굴 수 있는 활동
It's an anonymous video conference
익명의 화상회의입니다
By holding a video conference
화상회의를 개최하여
Let employees express their expectations and dissatisfaction with Se Yong
직원들이 세용에 대한 기대와 불만을 표현하도록 하세요.
Prepare a space where everyone can talk freely
모두가 자유롭게 이야기할 수 있는 공간을 준비하세요
Attendees basically use nicknames
참석자들은 기본적으로 닉네임을 사용합니다.
You can turn off the camera or mosaic it according to your own wishes
원하는 대로 카메라를 끄거나 모자이크 처리 할 수 있습니다.
It feels a lot like "100 Minutes Discussion" and can be changed to "Se Yong's 100 Minutes Discussion"
'100분 토론'과 느낌이 많이 비슷해서 '세용의 100분 토론'으로 바꿔도 됩니다.
"Seyong Citizens' Meeting"
"세용시민회의"
- Sounds super cliché. - So cliche.
- 너무 진부하게 들리네요 - 너무 진부해요.
"Se Yong, I want to know the truth."
"세용아, 나는 진실을 알고 싶다."
Not bad
나쁘지 않다
Let’s shorten this name to
이 이름을 다음과 같이 줄여보겠습니다.
"Shixiang", how about it?
"시샹", 어때요?
Not bad, "Shixiang"
나쁘지 않아요, "시샹"
Does everyone agree?
다들 동의하시나요?
agree
동의하다
agree!
동의하다!
Then the person in charge of Sehyang decided to be Agent Park?
그럼 세향 담당이 박요원이 되기로 했다는 건가요?
OK
좋아요
OK, if you want to conduct a video conference within the company system
OK, 회사 시스템 내에서 화상회의를 하고 싶다면
I still have to have a meeting with the computer team.
아직 컴퓨터 팀과 회의가 남아 있어요.
OK, end
알겠습니다. 종료합니다.
Are you OK?
괜찮으세요?
Well, it's okay
글쎄, 괜찮아
You seem to be dizzy a lot lately
요즘 많이 어지러운 것 같아
Have you been to the doctor?
의사에게 가본 적이 있나요?
I'll figure it out myself
내가 직접 알아낼게
Please, can the internal culture of the company be changed by filling out a few questionnaires?
몇 가지 설문지 를 작성하면 회사 내부 문화가 바뀔 수 있나요?
In my opinion, those people end up
내 생각엔 그런 사람들은 결국
Or will they use the company’s internal culture as an excuse to modify the evaluation mechanism ?
아니면 회사 내부 문화를 핑계로 평가 메커니즘을 수정 할까요?
Right?
오른쪽?
That’s why the talent will join
그렇기 때문에 인재가 합류하는 것입니다.
Even if the control lies with the public relations office, we are still indispensable.
비록 통제권이 홍보실에 있다고 해도 우리는 여전히 없어서는 안 될 존재입니다.
Even if that has nothing to do with the evaluation mechanism
그것이 평가 메커니즘과 관련이 없더라도
Will this year's group evaluation still proceed as usual?
올해도 조별 평가는 평소대로 진행되나요?
There is news that it will be suspended
중단된다는 소식이 있습니다
That kind of news is actually circulating?
그런 뉴스가 실제로 돌고 있는 걸까요?
What are you doing? It seems that employees are quite concerned about the internal culture improvement plan.
뭐하세요? 내부 문화 개선 방안에 대해 직원들의 우려가 꽤 있는 것 같습니다 .
This year’s group evaluation will still be conducted as usual
올해도 조별 평가는 평소대로 진행된다.
Even if they want to change, they can't do it overnight.
변화하고 싶어도 하루아침에 할 수는 없습니다.
Otherwise, how do they want to change the evaluation mechanism?
그렇지 않으면 평가 메커니즘을 어떻게 변경하고 싶습니까?
Is it going to be like other companies?
다른 회사와 같을까요?
Are employees allowed to give scores to their team leaders?
직원들이 팀 리더에게 점수를 줄 수 있나요?
I'm not responsible for the internal culture improvement plan so I don't know
내부 문화 개선 계획은 제가 담당하지 않아서 잘 모르겠습니다.
The leader of that project...
그 프로젝트의 리더는...
It’s Liu Jae-min’s agent from the Public Relations Team 2.
홍보2팀 류재민 에이전트입니다.
You should be very clear about his style of doing things.
당신은 그의 일 처리 스타일을 매우 분명하게 알아야 합니다.
He really chose the right side.
그는 정말로 옳은 쪽을 선택했습니다.
You should be nicer to him
그 사람에게 좀 더 친절해져야 해
How nice should I be to him?
나는 그 사람에게 얼마나 친절해야 할까?
I was just too good to him, so he dared to contradict me.
내가 그에게 너무 잘해줬기 때문에 그는 감히 내 말에 반박했다.
Young people these days are like that
요즘 젊은이들이 그렇죠
They are different from us
그들은 우리와 다르다
Companies and organizations are not everything to them
회사와 조직은 그들에게 전부가 아니다
Caimin, run quickly
카이민 빨리 달려
What?
무엇?
Hello, Xiao Meng
안녕하세요 멍샤오님
come here
이리 오세요
Damn it
젠장
Too late
너무 늦었어요
Oh my god
맙소사
Kill two birds with one stone
일석이조
Look who's here
누가 왔는지 봐봐
The pillars of Se Yong, the Three Musketeers who support Se Yong in moving forward.
세용의 전진을 뒷받침하는 삼총사 세용의 기둥.
Aren’t they the team leaders?
그 사람들 팀 리더 아닌가요?
-(Really, it's true)
-(정말이에요)
-(Absolutely sincere)
-(완전히 진심이다)
Senior Song, are you on the executive promotion list this time?
송 선배님, 이번에 임원 승진자 명단 에 오르셨나요 ?
Yes, that's right
네, 맞습니다
Me too!
저도요!
What?
무엇?
I also want to be a regular
나도 단골이 되고 싶다
Xuantai and I both need to be the executive
Xuantai와 나 둘 다 임원이 되어야 해
I'll let you be the executive. You can be the president if you want.
당신이 임원이 되도록 할게요 당신이 원한다면 대통령이 될 수도 있어요
good
좋은
You have to be a senior executive this time
이번에는 당신이 고위 임원이 되어야 합니다.
so…
그래서…
Try to win him over
그를 설득해 보세요
-(really )
-(정말 )
-Damn, you're so awesome . -You're so perfect.
- 젠장, 넌 정말 대단해 - 넌 정말 완벽해.
-You are simply a singer. -That's right, Chief Meng.
- 당신은 그저 가수일 뿐입니다 - 그렇죠, 멩 과장님.
Hello
안녕하세요
come here
이리 오세요
Come
오다
pick up
찾다
Drink this cup and all past grudges will be wiped out.
이 잔을 마시면 과거의 원한이 모두 사라질 것입니다.
do you know?
당신은 알고 있나요?
Brother Song, I want it too, I want to fuck you too
송 형제님, 나도 원해요, 나도 당신과 섹스하고 싶어요
You go away
가버려
Want a drink?
한잔 원하시나요?
Really
정말
drink
마시다
Hello! etc…
안녕하세요! 등…
Oh, you stinky boy
아, 냄새나는 놈아
Really
정말
Also let me feel the love of Brother Song
또한 송 형제님의 사랑을 느끼게 해주세요
Got it, brat
알았어, 얘야
hold
잡고 있다
Brother Song, let’s sing
송 형제님, 노래합시다
Why are you so presumptuous? Really deserve a beating
왜 그렇게 주제넘게 굴어요? 정말 때려야 마땅하다
Stop it, you brat
그만해, 이 새끼야
Come sing, sing
와서 노래해, 노래해
bring it on!
가져와!
Come on
어서 해봐요
(I feel uneasy)
(불편한 느낌이 든다)
(Someone is chasing me behind me)
(누군가 내 뒤에서 쫓아오고 있다)
(Standing at the edge of the dark cliff, I have no way to retreat)
(어두운 절벽 끝에 서서 후퇴할 길이 없다)
I love you, Song Xuantai
사랑해요, 송쉬안타이
Send Team Leader Cui home well
추이팀장을 집으로 잘 보내주세요
Captain Song, please take this car
송대장님, 이 차를 타주세요
Do you want to go somewhere else by yourself?
혼자서 다른 곳으로 가고 싶나요?
No such thing, I have to go to work tomorrow
그런 거 없어, 나 내일 출근해야 해
-Jai Min, I'm leaving . -Yes, please walk slowly.
- 재민 씨, 나 갈게요 - 네, 천천히 걸어주세요.
-Bye -Here, here you go
-안녕 -여기, 여기요
-Okay, I'm leaving . -Yes, please go slowly!
- 네, 나 갈게요 - 네, 천천히 가세요!
Oh, Team Leader Cui, please come here.
아, 추이 팀장님, 이리 오세요.
Come
오다
Oh, be careful...
아, 조심하세요...
Here, be careful
여기요, 조심하세요
It's time for Team Leader Jia to go home, come on
이제 팀장 지아가 집에 갈 시간이야 어서
Be careful!
조심하세요!
get home safe!
집에 안전하게 도착!
take care
잘 지내세요
what?
무엇?
Why don't you leave?
떠나는 게 어때?
Do you want to hire a taxi for you too?
당신도 택시를 빌리고 싶나요?
-Why are you so good at this kind of thing? -What?
- 당신은 왜 이런 일을 잘하는가? -무엇?
You're not willing, are you?
당신은 그럴 의지가 없군요, 그렇죠?
I really can't do that
난 정말 그럴 수 없어
You'll be fine when you become the section chief
과장이 되면 괜찮을 거야
Yeah?
응?
Well, we all are like that
뭐, 우리 모두는 그렇지
Because the people around me have been so virtuous since I joined the company.
제가 회사에 입사한 이후로 주변 사람들이 너무 덕이 많았거든요 .
correct
옳은
You probably don't know
아마 모르실 거예요
Because you are different from us
당신은 우리와 다르기 때문에
Really, you're drawing a line again.
정말, 당신은 다시 선을 긋고 있습니다.
I said that although I was born in the 1990s
90년대생인데도 말했잖아
But I am more like a person born in the 1980s
하지만 난 1980년대생에 더 가깝다
(Se Yong)
(세용)
(Shi Yong, want to know the truth)
(시용, 진실을 알고 싶어요)
"Worldly Thoughts"?
"세속적인 생각"?
Is it going well?
잘 진행되고 있나요?
We have notified all employees of the date and time
모든 직원에게 날짜와 시간을 통보했습니다 .
The video conferencing system has also been tested
화상 회의 시스템도 테스트되었습니다.
Even if people are outside the company, they can participate in the meeting through the link
회사 외부에 있더라도 링크를 통해 회의에 참여할 수 있습니다.
I am both looking forward to and curious about how the situation will develop in the end.
과연 상황이 어떻게 전개될지 기대도 되고 궁금하기도 합니다 .
But one thing I'm worried about is the number of attendees
그런데 한 가지 걱정되는 건 참석자 수다.
So I'm thinking about whether to make it mandatory
그래서 의무화할까 고민중이에요
Send one person from each group to participate
각 그룹에서 한 명씩 참여하도록 보내십시오.
No
아니요
Don't take a forced approach
억지로 접근하지 마세요
It is better to let employees participate voluntarily
직원들이 자발적으로 참여하도록 하는 것이 더 좋습니다.
The result of a few people voluntarily participating
소수의 자발적인 참여의 결과
Probably more than the hundreds of people who were forced to attend
아마 강제로 참석한 사람이 수백 명보다 많을 것입니다.
Comes more real
더욱 현실적으로 다가옵니다
I'm curious about any company that invites all employees to participate
전 직원을 참여시키는 회사가 있는지 궁금합니다.
Video conferencing?
화상 회의?
Probably not
아마도 그렇지 않을 것이다
Want a cup of tea?
차 한잔 원하시나요?
OK, I'd love to
알았어, 그러고 싶어
Director Gu!
구 감독님!
There is a guest waiting for you inside
안에 손님이 기다리고 있어요
But I don’t have an appointment with anyone today
그런데 오늘은 누구랑 약속도 없어
She said she is your daughter
그 사람이 당신 딸이라고 하더군요
Excuse me
실례합니다
It seems that tea will have to wait until next time.
차는 다음 시간까지 기다려야 할 것 같습니다.
no problem
괜찮아요
Feel sorry
유감
Hi
안녕
good
좋은
I've always been curious
나는 항상 궁금했어요.
What you do and where you work
당신이 하는 일과 일하는 곳
When you were in the United States, I couldn't see or know this.
당신이 미국에 있었을 때 나는 이것을 볼 수도 알 수도 없었습니다.
(Chief Public Relations Officer, Koo Yi-jung)
(홍보실 구이정)
"Chief Public Relations Officer, Goo Yi-jung"
"구이정 홍보실장"
-Yu Zhen... -Stop calling me all the time
- 유젠... - 나한테 맨날 전화하지 마
Don't come and pretend to be familiar with me until now
지금까지 와서 아는 척 하지마
Since you left because you wanted to live your own life , then continue to live like that
너 자신의 삶을 살고 싶어서 떠났으니 계속 그렇게 살아라.
Don't suddenly realize that you have a daughter now.
지금 당신에게 딸이 있다는 사실을 갑자기 깨닫지 마십시오 .
Pretend to care about me
나를 걱정하는 척
Really disgusting
정말 역겹다
By the way, I left early today just to tell you this.
그런데 오늘은 이 말을 하려고 일찍 나갔습니다.
Except for fainting from appendicitis in elementary school.
초등학교 때 맹장염으로 실신한 것 빼고요.
This is the first time I leave early
일찍 나가는 건 처음이야
Although you probably don't care at all whether I have an appendix or not
아마도 당신은 내가 맹장을 가지고 있든 없든 전혀 신경 쓰지 않을 것입니다.
You should say sorry at this time, right?
이때는 미안하다고 해야겠죠?
It's hard for you to even talk to me properly.
나한테 제대로 얘기하는 것조차 힘들어요.
How did you become a public relations expert?
어떻게 홍보 전문가가 되셨나요?
So chilling
너무 추워요
Where are you?
어디세요?
I also left early like you
나도 너처럼 일찍 떠났어
You said you were lying about menstrual pain.
생리통에 대해 거짓말을 했다고 하셨어요.
Where are you?
어디세요?
Hey, no, don't go that way, I'll tell you to come down!
야, 아니야, 그렇게 가지 마, 내려오라고 할게!
Just kill them all
그냥 다 죽여버려
Wait, hey!
잠깐, 이봐요!
hateful
증오스러운
Damn it, no matter what, I'm going to kill them all
젠장, 무슨 일이 있어도 다 죽여버릴 거야
So did you successfully meet the woman who abandoned you?
그럼 당신을 버린 여자는 성공적으로 만났나요 ?
Yeah, it went so damn well
응, 정말 잘 됐어
She can't even say a word
그 사람은 한마디도 못해요
Oh shit
아 젠장
You are not suitable for swearing at all
당신은 욕설에 전혀 적합하지 않습니다
Really? Is it awkward?
정말? 어색해요?
Yeah, so damn awkward
응, 존나 어색해
If you could learn swear words, I would have learned them long ago
네가 욕을 배울 수 있었다면 나도 오래 전에 배웠을 텐데
forget it
잊어 버려
swear words
욕설
This is not the place to rely
이곳은 의지할 곳이 아니다
The important thing is here
중요한 건 바로 여기에 있다
I see
알겠어요
It’s not easy to curse with curse words naturally
자연스럽게 욕하는 말로 욕하기 쉽지 않죠
Hey, behind the door!
이봐요, 문 뒤에 있어요!
where? I did not see it
어디? 나 못 봤어
Oops, I got hit.
아, 맞았어.
Hold on tight until I kill all those bastards
내가 그 새끼들을 다 죽일 때까지 꽉 잡아
I'll kill them all before I go to save you.
내가 널 구하러 가기 전에 다 죽여버릴 테니까.
you win
네가 이겼다
Task force matters
태스크포스의 문제
It should be done without interfering with your own duties, right?
본인의 업무에 지장을 주지 않고 이루어져야겠죠 ?
What?
무엇?
Because I see you've been doing that
왜냐면 당신이 그런 짓을 하고 있는 걸 봤거든요
Maybe you worked so hard because it was a project belonging to Director Goo .
아마도 구 감독님의 작품이라 너무 고생하셨을 것 같아요.
I did it without interfering with my duties.
나는 내 임무를 방해하지 않고 그것을 했다.
Then go here
그럼 여기로 가세요
"Social contribution plan"?
"사회공헌 계획"?
Located in Changwon?
창원에 위치?
You know our factory is there, right?
거기에 우리 공장이 있는 거 아시죠?
That activity is for regional development
그 활동은 지역 발전을 위한 것이다
We want to distribute nutritional supplements to residents in local communities
지역사회 주민들에게 영양제를 보급하고자 합니다.
In fact, it’s about being a volunteer
사실은 자원봉사를 하는 것인데
It's up to you this time
이번에는 당신에게 달렸습니다
Our group needs to send one person to manage the distribution of items.
우리 그룹에서는 물품 배포를 관리 하기 위해 한 사람을 보내야 합니다 .
Also help with taking photos
사진 촬영에도 도움을 주세요
But the person in charge here is you...
그런데 여기 담당자는 당신이군요...
Let's share the work together
함께 일을 나누자
Aren't we in the same group?
우리 같은 그룹 아닌가?
how? You do not want it?
어떻게? 당신은 그것을 원하지 않습니까?
No matter what, I am still considered your superior.
무슨 일이 있어도 나는 여전히 당신의 상사로 간주됩니다.
Ryu Jae-min is the agent!
류재민이 에이전트다!
-Yes -Agent Qi, you are here too
- 네 - 치 요원님도 오셨어요
Yes, Team Leader Song
네, 송팀장입니다
I want to bring Agent Liu back to our group
Liu 요원을 우리 그룹으로 다시 데려오고 싶습니다
Because the sales manager has been complaining about not having him
영업관리자가 그 사람이 없다고 불평했기 때문에
The press releases are a mess
보도자료가 엉망이네요
right?
오른쪽?
They think we just copied the product description
그들은 우리가 제품 설명을 복사했다고 생각해요
It's not a press release at all.
전혀 보도자료가 아닙니다.
Do you know that you also misspelled words?
당신도 단어 철자가 틀린 것을 알고 있습니까?
Do you understand?
이해했나요?
Come back to our group
우리 그룹으로 돌아와
yes
예
Hello, Chief Meng!
안녕하세요, 맹실장님!
Hand over the protein powder case to Agent Liu
리우요원에게 단백질 파우더 케이스를 넘겨주세요
Because the product formula needs to be promoted again after the upgrade, I need the right person to be in charge.
업그레이드 후 제품 공식을 다시 홍보해야 하기 때문에 담당자가 필요합니다.
Hey, do you understand? Why don't you answer me?
이봐, 이해됐어? 왜 나에게 대답하지 않는거야?
knew
알고 있었다
besides
게다가
Is the internal culture improvement plan going smoothly?
내부문화개선계획은 순조롭게 진행되고 있나요?
Yes
예
Well, you'll do well because you're pretty smart.
글쎄요, 당신은 꽤 똑똑하니까 잘 할 거예요.
If you encounter any difficulties during implementation, just tell me.
구현 중에 어려움이 있으면 알려주십시오.
i will help you
내가 당신을 도울 것입니다
OK
좋아요
He is really fickle and erratic in doing things
그 사람은 일을 하는 데 있어서 정말 변덕스럽고 변덕스럽습니다
(Senteng 100 high protein milkshake product introduction)
(센텡 100 고단백 밀크쉐이크 제품소개)
(Mori Teng 100)
(모리 100)
(Features of Senteng 100 high protein milkshake)
(센텡 100 고단백 밀크쉐이크의 특징)
(Genzyme praise)
(젠자임 칭찬해)
(Welcome! You have joined this forum!)
(환영합니다! 이 포럼에 가입하셨습니다!)
(Nutritional Supplement Reviews)
(영양 보충제 리뷰)
(Is Senteng 100 high protein milkshake different from before?)
(센텡100 고단백 밀크쉐이크는 기존과 다른가요?)
(I saw many comments saying that my skin will be itchy or my stomach will hurt after drinking it ...)
(마시면 피부가 가렵다거나 배가 아프다는 댓글을 많이 봤어요 ...)
(Does the Senteng 100 high protein milkshake produced by Serong taste good?)
(세롱에서 생산하는 센텡100 고단백 밀크셰이크 맛있나요?)
( What happened to Serong’s Senteng 100 comments recently ?)
( 최근 세롱이의 센텡 100개 댓글 에 무슨 일이 있었던 걸까요 ?)
(Has anyone ever drank Shirong’s high-protein milkshake? Is your stomach okay? Is your intestines normal?)
(시롱 고단백 밀크쉐이크 드셔보신 분 계신가요? 배는 괜찮으신가요? 장은 괜찮으신가요?)
( Severe side effects occurred after drinking Serong Senteng 100 high protein milkshake , be sure to read it!)
( 세롱센텡 100 고단백 밀크셰이크를 마신 후 심각한 부작용이 발생하였으니 꼭 읽어주세요!)
(send message)
(문자 보내)
Hello, I am agent Yoo Jae-min from Seyong Public Relations Group.
안녕하세요. 세용홍보그룹 유재민 에이전트입니다.
Could I please meet with you to find out more about it?
좀 더 자세히 알아보기 위해 당신을 만나서 이야기를 나눌 수 있을까요?
Any more details on side effect symptoms?
부작용 증상에 대한 자세한 내용은 없나요?
looking forward to your reply
귀하의 회신을 기대하겠습니다
Didn’t you leave the protein powder case to me?
단백질 파우더 케이스는 나한테 맡기지 않았어 ?
It's too hard for you alone. Let's do it together with Agent Park.
혼자서는 너무 힘드네요. 박요원과 함께 해보세요.
Agent Park, have you dealt with protein powder related products before?
박 에이전트님, 예전에 단백질 파우더 관련 제품을 다뤄보신 적 있으신가요 ?
Yes, you mean high protein bread?
네, 고단백 빵 말씀이신가요?
Yes, that product is very popular, right?
네, 그 제품이 인기가 많죠?
There is a correlation between the two, right?
둘 사이에는 상관관계가 있는 거죠, 그렇죠?
But this is my first case
하지만 이건 내 첫 번째 사건이야
Yes, I know too
응, 나도 알아
I just want you to do it together.
그냥 같이 했으면 좋겠어요.
I hope that I will be the main person in charge
내가 주 책임자가 되기를 바란다.
I will try my best to help Jihyo from the side
옆에서 지효를 돕기 위해 최선을 다하겠습니다
She has been working on it for a while. It would be better for her to be the main person in charge.
그녀가 한동안 그 일을 해왔기 때문에 그녀가 주요 책임자가 되는 것이 더 나을 것이다.
Okay, you two can decide for yourselves , but no matter who is in charge
좋아, 너희 둘이 스스로 결정할 수 있지만 , 누가 책임자인지는 상관없어
Responsibility must be borne by those with higher rankings
책임은 높은 사람이 져야 한다
knew
알고 있었다
Go ahead
계속하세요
This is the future plan
앞으로의 계획은 이렇습니다
Everything has been finalized and is in progress.
모든 것이 마무리되어 진행 중입니다.
Chi Hyo
치효
I will really only do what you tell me
난 정말 네 말대로만 할 거야
As long as you make good use of me, I should be very helpful to you.
당신이 나를 잘 활용한다면 나는 당신에게 큰 도움이 될 것입니다.
I have strong working ability
나는 일하는 능력이 강하다
All decisions and judgments are mine. Please don’t have any opinions.
모든 결정과 판단은 나의 것입니다. 어떤 의견도 가지지 마십시오.
There will be a Shixiang drill in 30 minutes. See you in conference room A.
30분 후에 Shixiang 훈련이 있을 예정입니다. 회의실 A에서 만나요.
(Senteng 100 high protein milkshake online promotion and marketing strategy plan)
(센텡 100 고단백 밀크셰이크 온라인 프로모션 및 마케팅 전략 기획)
(Lee Seung-hee, HR Lee Yeon-sung)
(이승희, HR 이연성)
That's it
그게 다야
Seung Hee, can you see me?
승희야, 나 보여?
Yes, you can see it clearly
응, 확실히 알 수 있지
There seems to be no problem with the connection
연결에는 문제가 없을 것 같습니다
Can you see me?
나를 볼 수 있나요?
Yeah, I can hear it. The connection status is pretty good.
네, 들려요. 연결 상태는 꽤 좋습니다.
Can you see me too?
나도 볼 수 있나요?
Yes, you can see it
네, 볼 수 있어요
Please turn off the camera
카메라를 꺼주세요
OK, wait a moment
알았어, 잠깐만
(Lee Seung-hee, HR Lee Yeon-sung)
(이승희, HR 이연성)
What do you think about adding a note next to the nickname?
닉네임 옆에 메모를 추가하는 것에 대해 어떻게 생각하시나요?
How long have you lived in this world?
당신은 이 세상에서 얼마나 오래 살았나요?
Although it is an anonymous meeting , adding seniority should be helpful.
익명의 모임이지만 선배를 추가하는 것이 도움이 될 것입니다.
Um
음
Okay, that's it
알았어, 그게 다야
Is it okay?
괜찮나요?
is very good
아주 좋다
But there will still be some lag, right?
하지만 여전히 약간의 지연이 있을 것입니다. 그렇죠?
Yes, that phenomenon...
응 그 현상은...
I go first
내가 먼저 가
-Okay, thank you for your hard work . -Thank you for your hard work.
-알겠습니다. 수고해 주셔서 감사합니다 . -수고해 주셔서 감사합니다.
Isn't tomorrow the weekend?
내일은 주말 아닌가요?
Saturday 2pm
토요일 오후 2시
What if everyone runs out to play and no one really wants to participate?
모두가 놀러 갔는데 아무도 참여하고 싶어하지 않는다면 어떻게 될까요?
Xiao Zhao
샤오 자오
Don't have high expectations
큰 기대는 하지 마세요
Everyone is willing to listen to this matter about Se Yong
모두가 세용에 관한 이 문제를 듣고 싶어합니다
Not quite used to it yet
아직은 익숙하지 않아요
Yes, after all we have tried our best
네, 결국 우리는 최선을 다했습니다
Hello, Xiao Zhao
안녕하세요, 샤오자오 님
that…
저것…
Doesn't it count that you said you wanted to keep your distance from me ?
나한테 거리를 두고 싶다고 말한 게 중요한 게 아닌가 ?
Well, I'm sorry for this period of time
글쎄요, 그동안 미안했어요
Don't you need more time?
시간이 더 필요하지 않나요?
I feel better once I focus on my work
일에 집중하고 나면 기분이 좋아진다
It seems you are really hopeless
넌 정말 절망적인 것 같아
What is work?
일이란 무엇입니까?
That is to say
즉 말하자면
Anyway, to celebrate we are friends again
어쨌든, 축하하기 위해 우리는 다시 친구가 되었습니다
How about eating pork knuckles with soju?
돼지갈비에 소주를 곁들여 먹으면 어떨까요?
I have an appointment
약속이 있어요
With whom?
누구 랑?
Representative Xu
쉬 대표
- He asked me to meet and said he had something to say - right?
- 만나자고 하고 할 말이 있다고 하더군요 - 그렇죠?
Then I'll go too, let's go
그럼 나도 갈게 가자
What are you going to do? you crazy
당신은 무엇을 할 예정입니까? 너 미쳤어
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
Hey, isn’t it just a meal?
야, 그냥 식사 아니야?
How can you call me crazy...
어떻게 나를 미쳤다고 할 수 있니?
Hey, why can't I follow?
야, 난 왜 따라갈 수 없지?
Why did you choose a pig's trotters shop?
족발 가게를 선택한 이유는 무엇인가요?
I just heard someone talking about pig's feet, which made me want to eat them suddenly.
방금 누군가가 족발 이야기를 하는 걸 듣고 갑자기 먹고 싶어졌어요.
That's it
그게 다야
There are obviously many places with good atmosphere
분명 분위기 좋은 곳이 많을 텐데
Representative Xu, please sit here.
쉬 대표님, 여기 앉아주세요.
good
좋은
Do you want to sit there?
거기 앉으시겠어요?
Delicious
맛있는
What do you want to say to me?
나에게 무슨 말을 하고 싶나요?
I feel very grateful for what happened that night
나는 그날 밤 일어난 일에 대해 매우 감사함을 느낀다
Were you injured trying to take care of me?
나를 돌보려다 부상을 입었나요?
No, that's nothing, I forgot about it
아니, 그건 아무것도 아니야, 잊어버렸어
It’s best to forget what happened while drinking
술 마시면 잊어버리는 게 상책
I really can't forget it
정말 잊을 수가 없어요
That's understandable
그건 이해할 수 있어요
After all, falling down among the rose bushes is not a common thing.
결국, 장미 덤불 사이로 떨어지는 것은 흔한 일이 아닙니다.
so i want to ask you
그래서 나는 당신에게 묻고 싶습니다.
Um
음
Should we go on a formal date?
우리 정식 데이트하러 갈까?
What?
무엇?
What is he doing?
그는 무엇을 하고 있나요?
Do you want to invite me on a date now?
지금 나를 데이트에 초대하시겠습니까?
right
오른쪽
I…
나…
have a crush on you
너에게 반했어
Why are you so excited?
왜 그렇게 흥분해요?
good
좋은
I do
그래요
let's go on a date
데이트하러 가자
Subtitle translation: Chen Yiying
자막 번역: Chen Yiying